I just felt the need to come on here and remind y'all that Jasmine Crockett has been on my podcast, Small Doses.
Y'all, I am joined here with Representative Jasmine Crockett of Dallas, Texas.
And y'all, our episode, Side Effects of Gathering the Government, which she does on a regular basis, is now live wherever you get your podcasts.
Please make sure to go and listen because you're saying the things.
I'm trying.
You're doing.
We working.
Like, y'all be acting like I'm just out here on everybody.
No, I give people burn until they burn out.
And if you do not actively and ardently state that you are against Israel, against the genocide, against the usage of taxpayer dollars to fund the Israel economy, against taking money from corporate PACs.
All of these things are reasons why I will rescind support of somebody who is seeking political position.
The biggest issue is that when many people see someone that looks or acts like them running for office, they think that they need to protect them because those people will protect them.
And that's just simply not the case.
And to be quite honest, it's not even like it's not the case because they don't want to.
But the truth of the matter is they are moving into a system that will not allow them to.
So unless they are actively and loudly dismantling that system, they are not doing anything to change the way that system is affecting you.
Better way to enslave a man than give him the vote and call him free.
I think the vote can only be used as a tool of organization.
We can only use the vote to organize our people.
Now, to really believe that we can put someone in office and that these people would be responsive to our needs is naïve, politically naïve.
Because even if one of the black candidates who ran for office was to take the office of president, then black people must be prepared to fight against that person.
Because, you see, the system mandates the action of the individual.
The individual does not determine how this country will function.
This country works off the military-industrial complex, which means that it's profitable to wage war.
And unless you devise another plan or another scheme to sustain or to boost this economy, then it's going to be necessary to wage war, whether a black individual is in office or a white individual is in office.
Well, we're talking about a complete change in system.
Support a real one.